[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Бігати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "走ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пригати, стрибати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "跳びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Лізти, карапкатись, підніматись' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "登ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Махати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "振ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пірнати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "潜ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Натискати, штовхати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "押します"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стукати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "叩きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Падати, валитись' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "転びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кидати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "投げます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Піднімати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持ち上げます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Озирнутися' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "振り向きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стати дибом, стати на руки' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "逆立ちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'протилежний, навпаки' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "逆"
    }
]